altfg.com 2017-06-06

# Terms of Use / Privacy Policy – Alt Film Guide

## Terms of Use / Disclaimer

The information found at Alt Film Guide (“We,” “The Website”) is for general information purposes only. While We endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, We make NO representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability (age-related or otherwise), or availability with respect to The Website itself or the information, products, services, images, or graphics found on The Website for any purpose.

Additionally, bear in mind that We make NO representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the content of external websites linked to from Alt Film Guide, whether those links are found in ads or in Alt Film Guide posts. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or an endorsement of either the material contained or the views expressed on other sites. If you click on any external link, whether or not We warn you of potentially unsuitable content, you're doing so at your own risk.

Also bear in mind that the content found on The Website, including its Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, may be changed/revised or removed at any time without warning.

And finally, you affirm that you are over the age of 13. If you are under 13, you are not authorized to access Alt Film Guide.

If you do not agree with these Terms of Use, leave The Website now.

## Privacy Policy

Alt Film Guide uses cookies to record the number of unique visits to our website and to measure general traffic patterns. No personally identifiable information is collected in that manner. By “non-personally identifiable information” we mean that your name, address, email address, or telephone number is NOT collected. For more information about cookies, visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>.

Bear in mind that our advertising partners use third-party advertising companies that may employ cookie technology to measure advertisement effectiveness and may collect information about user visits to the Alt Film Guide. Those third-party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our site, other websites, and other forms of media so as to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you.

For more information on our ad servers' cookies, visit:

Note: In the future, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. In case our cookie use or data collection changes at some time in the future, we will update our website to notify you of these changes.

You may opt out from such collection via opt-out services such as the Network Advertising Initiative <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.
